(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-11T14:43:25.580943",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
バイのバイのバイのバイのバイバイ感電中！
Multiplied over and over, electric shock!
本音と建て前無い私
I have no facade between my true thoughts and words,
成りた、降りたいけどだけど
I want to be, I want to step down, but... but...
人の目気にせず素直な子
An honest kid who doesn't care what others think,
成りた、降りたいけどだけど
I want to be, I want to step down, but... but...
誰かを救うということは 過去の自分を救うことです
Saving someone else means saving your past self.
誰かを愛すということは 本当の自分を大好きになることです
Loving someone else means truly loving your true self.
バイバイバイバイバイバイバイバイ
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye,
何回転んでも立ち上がれ
get back up no matter how many times you fall!
バイバイバイバイバイバイバイバイ
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye,
厄介な問題も閉じ込めろ
lock away all your troublesome problems too!
バイバイバイバイバイバイバイバイ
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye,
悲しい？ほらバイのバイのバイのバイで、もっと遠くへ！
feeling sad? Hey, with double-doubling, let's go further!
飽き性根性ない状況
Lacking staying power and grit in this situation,
やめたいやめたいけどだけど
I want to quit, I want to quit, but... but...
もっぱらネガティブ頭脳が駆しこ
My pessimistic brain is running full speed,
やめたいやめたいけどだけど
I want to quit, I want to quit, but... but...
何かを犠牲にすることは 何かを目指すということです
Making sacrifices means aiming for something.
何かを目指すということは 何かを本気で信じるということです
Aiming for something means truly believing in it with all your heart.
バイバイバイバイバイバイバイバイ
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye,
なんて無責任なこの人生
what an irresponsible life this is!
バイバイバイバイバイバイバイバイ
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye,
だって私たちは私だもん楽しい！
because I am who I am, and it's fun!
バイバイバイバイバイバイバイバイ
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye,
ほらバイのバイのバイのバイでもっと遠くへ！
hey, with double-doubling, let's go even further!
バイバイバイバイバイバイバイバイ
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye,
バイのバイのバイのバイバイ感電中！
multiplied over and over, electric shock!
バイバイバイバイバイバイバイバイ
Bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye-bye,
バイのバイのバイのバイバイ感電中！
multiplied over and over, electric shock!
義理を大事に本音を大事に
Cherishing duty, cherishing true feelings,
素直に行ったってバイバイファイ！
living honestly, bye-bye-fight!
強い人間になりたかったって
Wanting to become a strong person,
今からなれるさバイバイファイ！
you can become one starting now, bye-bye-fight!
有言実行言葉に宿った
Action matching words, trusting the soul
魂信じてバイバイファイ！
dwelling in your words, bye-bye-fight!
誰かと比べて落ち込んだって
Even if you get down comparing yourself to others,
自分は自分さバイバイファイ！
you are yourself, bye-bye-fight!
ド・キ・ド・キ・して rouge ？
Do-ki-do-ki, pounding rouge?
いくますよー
Let's go ~
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！
Innocent, innocent, innocent beautiful girl!
マリン！マリン！マリンは無罪！
Marine, marine, marine is innocent!
やっぱキラキラもっとクラクラ
As expected, sparkling makes me dizzy ~
「ねぇ、言ったよね？ 年齢なんて関係ないってさ そういう面倒くささも含めて愛してくれるって」
"Hey, didn't you say it? Age doesn't matter, right? You promised to love me with all the hassle too"
「ねぇねぇ、言ったよね？ 一点愛？ ふう、そういうこと言うんだ」
"Hey, hey, didn't you say it? Or not? Hmm, so that's how it is?"
「ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますけど？」
"Oh, by the way, on this ship, the innocent beautiful girl law applies, you know?"
まさか！魔法で若返り（若返り）
No way! Rejuvenated by magic (rejuvenated ~)
秘密の素顔は君にだけ
My true face is only for you
「特別ですって？」
"This is special, you know ~?"
(Ah) あたし厄介よ
(Ah) I'm a bit troublesome
(Ah) 港なんかじゃい
(Ah) The port isn't exciting enough
はしゃげないわ最近はね
I can't have fun there lately
宝の島にしてほしい気分（出航ー！）
I want you to make this a treasure island! (Set sail —!)
キュートは正義美少女無罪
Cute is justice, innocent beautiful girl
キミの一番目指してヨーソロー！
I'll aim to be number one in your heart, yo-ho-ho ~
本当は自信ないけどがんばっちゃう（Ahoy！）
Actually I lack confidence, but I'll do my best! (Ahoy!)
きゅきゅきゅるん、きゅきゅきゅるるん
Kyu, kyu, kyu run ~, Kyu, kyu, kyu run run ~
恋する気持ち１７才
Falling in love, my heart feels 17 years old
てっぺんになっちゃうわオトナの時間
When midnight comes, it's time to be an adult
（やっぱキラキラもっとクラクラ）
(sparkling, more dizzy)
ド・キ・ド・キ・して rouge ？
Do-ki-do-ki, pounding rouge?
まだ早い
Still too early!
だ・だ・だめですか？
Da-da, is it no good?
フリルのお召着たら（「そんなことないよ」）
If I wear ruffled clothes? (Not really)
だ・だ・だって魔法少女になってみたい（ギリギリ有罪！？）
Da-da, but I want to be a magical girl! (Barely guilty!?)
進路は南南西、ちょっぴり足りない積極性？
Course? Heading south-southwest, a bit lacking in aggressiveness?
結局キミももっと若い子？
In the end you also prefer younger girls?
「なんたってするから見捨てないで、きみたち！」
"I'll do anything! Don't abandon me, everyone!"
（ちょっといいとこ見てみたい）
(Can I show off a little?)
(Ah) たまにいじけちゃう
(Ah) Sometimes I sulk
(Ah) それでもいいの？
(Ah) Is that still okay with you?
年齢だもん本気にしてしまう
At this age, I get easily emotional
嵐の中も（一緒に行こう？）（出航ー！）
Even if a storm hits / Will you stay with me? (Set sail —!)
ハートにチャーム美少女無罪
Charm in my heart, innocent beautiful girl
あれあれどうしちゃった？めんどくさいかなんて言っちゃってって
Eh, why? Why are you suddenly acting grumpy?
かまってくれるキミが好き（Ahoy！）
But I know you still care about me! (Ahoy!)
きゅきゅきゅるん、きゅきゅきゅるるん
Kyu, kyu, kyu run ~, Kyu, kyu, kyu run run ~
やさしくしてね１７才
Be nice to me, okay? I'm 17 years old ~
突っ込んで経験値お楽しみ中
Gaining experience, let's enjoy chu ~
（やっぱキラキラもっとクラクラ）
(sparkling, more dizzy)
ド・キ・ド・キ・して rouge ？
Do-ki-do-ki, pounding rouge?
「あーあ、お湯割りすこだい！このマリンの…」
"Ahhh... Forgive me This Marine's charm..."
魅力！魔力！不可抗力！
Magic? Appeal? Inevitable!
「…罪な女」ね？
I'm a sinful woman, aren't I?
離さないでつかまっていて
Don't let go of me, hold on tight
世界の広さ見せてあげるから（出航ー！）
I'll show you how big the world is (Set sail —!)
キュートは正義美少女無罪
Cute is justice, innocent beautiful girl
キミの一番目指してヨーソロー！
I'll aim to be number one in your heart, yo-ho-ho ~
冗談も大好きだけど真剣よ（Ahoy！）
I love joking, but my feelings are real (Ahoy!)
きゅきゅきゅるん、きゅきゅきゅるるん
Kyu, kyu, kyu run ~, Kyu, kyu, kyu run run ~
恋する気持ち１７才
Falling in love, my heart feels 17 years old
てっぺんになっちゃうわオトナの時間
When midnight comes, it's time to be an adult
（やっぱキラキラもっとクラクラ）
(sparkling, more dizzy)
ド・キ・ド・キ・して rouge ？
Do-ki-do-ki, pounding rouge?
まだ早い
Still too early!
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！
Innocent, innocent, innocent beautiful girl!
マリン！マリン！マリンは無罪！
Marine, marine, marine is innocent!
やっぱキラキラもっとクラクラ
As expected, sparkling makes me dizzy ~
【“マリン”ではなく、“マリン船長”だろうん！？】
It's not just "Marine"... It's "Captain Marine", right?!
はーい、君たち！7周年記念ライブ始まりましたねー！
Hi everyone! The 7th anniversary 3D live has begun!
ハッシュタグは、えー、こちら！こちら！こちら！宝鐘マリン7周年3Dライブになっております！
The hashtag is, um, right here! Right here! Right here! #HoushouMarine7thAnniversary3DLive!
このあとね、知ってると思うけど、うーん、水着のお披露目がありますので、3D水着、うー、楽しみでしょ？
After this, you probably know, um, there's the swimsuit reveal, so 3D swimwear, ugh, aren't you excited?
いっぱいスクショして、ツイートしてく…あ、ポストしてください！ポストしてください！
Take lots of screenshots and tweet... ah, post it! Please post it!
ここから先もまだまだ、えー、素敵なゲストの皆さんが来ますので、いったいどんな曲、どんなパフォーマンスをするのか、超々楽しみにして、そして水着もどんな感じなのか、
From here on, um, wonderful guests will still be coming, so I'm super duper excited to see what songs and performances they'll do, and what the swimsuits will be like!
サブもあるからね、あのサブも全部見切ってから、見切ってくださいね！そして素敵な、うん、グッズもね、マリンがいっぱい考えたグッズとかもありますんで、
There are also subs, so make sure you check out all the subs too! And we also have wonderful goods that Marine thought a lot about, so...
さあ、どんどん楽しんで、行きましょうー！行くぞー！
Now, let's keep having fun! Let's go! Let's go!
ロンディ・ダリ・ダリ・カリー・コーリー 金を鳴らせばこの通り これが終焉のRequiem
Londi dari dari kali kory, if you ring the bell, just like this, this is the requiem of the end.
せーのっ 触ったら逮捕！（Ah!） 極chu❤de!点呼！（Uh!） いち以上にーさんしー？（ごめんなさいー）
Ready, set, touch and you're arrested! (Ah!) Roll call with extreme chu❤de! (Uh!) One, two, three, four? (I'm sorry ~)
はぁ！？(ﾟДﾟ)ごめんなさいが、聞こえなーい（えー！）
Ha? (ﾟДﾟ) I can't hear your apology (E~!)
粛聖！！ロリ神レクイエム☆ 将来は お前なんかに 好かれたくない（ない！）
Purification!! Loli-kami Requiem☆ In the future, I don't want to be liked by someone like you (No!)
泥水で 口を洗え 法廷で 会おうね❤（ねっ）
Wash your mouth out with muddy water, see you in court?❤ (Right?)
さぁ おまわりさん 連れて行って 妄想しか取り柄のない かわいいそお人（ういいちゃん！ういいちゃん！待ってよおういいちゃん！）
Come on, Mr. Policeman, take me away, a pitiful person whose only redeeming quality is delusion (Ui-chan! Ui-chan! Wait for me, Ui-chan!)
その姿貌に見せられますが？（ういいちゃん！ういいちゃん！かわいいういいちゃん！）わぁ、ありがとうございます、お疲れ様です^^
Can you show that figure to your parents? (Ui-chan! Ui-chan! So cute!) Waa, thank you, good job~^^
ロリロリ神、降臨（ずっきゅーん！） マジババ奴等に用心（ばっきゅーん！）
Loli-loli god, descends (Zukkyun!) Beware of seriously dangerous creeps (Bakkyun!)
まともじゃないなら 早く消えてください
If you're not normal, please disappear quickly
ロリロリ神、降臨（ずっきゅーん！） 鐘を鳴らせばこの通り（yes!）
Lovely loli-loli god, descends (Zukkyun!) If you ring the bell, just like this (Yes!)
とても優しくて 素敵なお兄ちゃん 楽園でホラ ねんねしな
Such a kind and wonderful big brother, hooray, go to sleep in paradise
（ういいちゃん…）ほら。世の中には、こんなに気持ち悪い人たちが蔓延しているんですっ！みんな、晒しageます。（ういいちゃん…うい、こっち向いてぇ～頭～）
(Ui-chan...) Look. In this world, such disgusting people are running rampant! Everyone, I'm going to expose you. (Ui-chan... Ui, look over here~~)
触ったら逮捕！（Ah!） 極chu❤de!点呼！（Uh!） いち以上にーさんしー？（ごめんなさいー） はぁ！？(ﾟДﾟ)ごめんなさいが、聞こえなーい（えー！）
Touch and you're arrested! (Ah!) Roll call with extreme chu❤de! (Uh!) One, two, three, four? (I'm sorry ~) Ha? (ﾟДﾟ) I can't hear your apology (E~!)
粛聖！！ロリ神レクイエム☆ はぁーい、獄中にいるみなしゃーん
Purification!! Loli-kami Requiem☆ Hiiii, everyone in prison ~
刑務所ファンミーティングの時間でぇーす その、腐りきった耳をゴリゴリかっぽじって よおーく聞いてくださいね
It's prison fan meeting time ~ Clean out those rotten ears thoroughly and listen carefully, okay?
ざこ（助かる～ぅ） きもきも（助かる～ぅ） うるさい（助かる～ぅ） 黙ってもらっていいですか？ 嫌いです（助かる～ぅ） かわいそ（助かる～ぅ） だーさ よーわっ みっともな～w どうしようもない お兄ちゃんお姉ちゃん もう希望もない ゴミだオメェラ 汚物消毒百態番固有結界発動
Zako (Saved~u) Kimo-kimo (Saved~u) Noisy (Saved~u) Can you please shut up? I hate you (Saved~u) Pitiful (Saved~u) Loser, weakling, pathetic~w Hopeless big brothers and big sisters You're garbage with no hope left Filth disinfection 110, reality marble activation
粛聖☆ういビーム（あーーーーーーっ！） もういちっ！ういビーム（あーーーーーーっ！） まだまだまだぁっ！ういビーム（あーーーーーーっ！） ういビーム（あーーーーーーっ！）
Purification☆Ui Beam (Aaaaaaa!) Once more! Ui Beam (Aaaaaaa!) Still more! Ui Beam (Aaaaaaa!) Ui Beam (Aaaaaaa!)
怒りの日。聖なるインターネットに、血の雨が降りそうそいだ日。愚かなロリコンを骨の髄まで浄化する、一筋の光。それが、ういビームなのである。「ういは、すべてを許します…」
Day of wrath. The day a rain of blood fell on the sacred internet. A single ray of light purifying foolish lolicon to the bone. That is the Ui Beam. "Ui forgives everything..."
ああ、この世の醜さを集めて描いてみる まっ白なキャンバスが汚れて泣いている Lovely 振り向いた少女は そっと手を掴む 「楽園などないから」
Ah, I'll collect the ugliness of this world and try to paint it. The pure white canvas is crying because it's stained. Lovely, the turning girl gently grabs your hand. "Because there is no paradise"
おっきな友達のみんなへ お前らが打ち込んでいる虚無には、何の意義があるのか？ ねえ、教えてよ。うい、ぜーんぜんかんずなんだ！
To all you big kids out there, what meaning is there in the void you are pouring into? Hey, tell me. Ui doesn't understand at all!
ロリロリ神、降臨（ずっきゅーん！） さよなら笑顔でバイバイ（ばっきゅーん！） ピリオドをどうぞ この手で押してあげよ
Loli-loli god, descends (Zukkyun!) Goodbye with a smile, bye-bye (Bakkyun!) Please let me press the period with this hand
Lovely ロリロリ神、降臨（ずっきゅーん！） 鐘を鳴らせばこの通り（yes!） とても優しくて 素敵なお兄ちゃん 楽園でホラ ねんねしな
Lovely loli-loli god, descends (Zukkyun!) If you ring the bell, just like this (Yes!) Such a kind and wonderful big brother, hooray, go to sleep in paradise
たすかる！
Lifesaver!
うるさい！
Shut up!
だから黙っててもらっていいですか？
Can you please just stay quiet?
かわいいです。
You're cute.
かわいいぞ！
So cute!
どうした？
What's wrong?
言う事もねえな
Nothing much to say.
出す用もない
Nothing to put out either.
お兄ちゃんお姉ちゃん
Big brothers, big sisters,
待ち構えんマネーゴン
get ready, money gone!
見せたおめぇら
Show it to you all,
アブソリュート100%パーダー！
Absolute 100% plunder!
この夕景に初・ト・ア！
In this evening view, first time... ah!
この世の醜さを 集めて描いてみるよ
Gathering the ugliness of this world, I'll try to sketch it out.
真っ白なタンバリン 深く手を出して
With a pure white tambourine, reaching out deep inside.
誰もが逃げ出している ロンリフリーむいた少女は
The lonely, carefree girl that everyone runs away from
そっと手を掴む 楽園などないから
gently grabs your hand, because there is no paradise.
年中無休だから
Open all year round, so...
大きなお友達のみんなへ
To all our big friends out there,
お前らが打ち込んでいる虚無には何の意義があるの？
what meaning is there in the void you're pouring yourselves into?
ねえ、教えてよ マリ、全然 わかんないんだ
Hey, tell me, Marine, I totally don't get it.
ロリロリ神カーニバル さようなら笑顔でバイバイ
Loli Loli God Carnival, say goodbye with a smile, bye-bye!
ピリオドのその先
Beyond the period,
この手で押してあげよう
I'll push it for you with this hand.
ラビングロリロリ神カーニバル
Loving Loli Loli God Carnival,
金を慣らしてはこの通り
ringing the gold just like this.
とっても優しくて 素敵な女の子
A very kind and wonderful girl,
楽園でほろねえ年娘は
the girl who won't wither in paradise
それが救いさ レグイエム
that is salvation, Requiem.
無罪 無罪 美少女無罪 マリ マリ マリン
Innocent, innocent, bishoujo innocent, Mari, Mari, Marine!
毎回 無罪 無罪 美少女無罪 うい うい おいは無罪
Every time innocent, innocent, bishoujo innocent, Ui, Ui, Ui is innocent!
毎回 無罪 無罪 美少女無罪 うい うい おいらは無罪
Every time innocent, innocent, bishoujo innocent, Ui, Ui, I am innocent!
ねえ、言ったよね 年齢なんて関係ないってさ
Hey, you said age doesn't matter, right?
そういうめんどくさいのも含めて愛してくれるって ねぇ、言ったよね？言えない？
That you'd love me including all that troublesome stuff too—hey, did you say that? Can't say?
任せて！魔法で若返り
Leave it to me! Rejuvenated by magic,
ヒミツの素顔はキミにだけ トクベツですよ？
my secret true face is special just for you, okay?
ああ...あたし厄介だわ ああ...港なんかじゃ
Ah... I'm a pain. Ah... not just any port,
はしゃげないわ 近頃はね 宝の島にしてほしい気分
I can't get too excited lately, I feel like making it an island of treasure!
キュートは正義 美少女無罪 キミの一番目指してヨーソロ！
Cute is justice, bishoujo innocent, aiming for your number one, yosoro!
本当は自信ないけど頑張っちゃう
I'm actually not confident, but I'll do my best
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん きゅっ きゅっ きゅるんるん
Kyu kyu kyurun, kyu kyu kyurunrun,
0時にになっちゃうわ オトナの時間
it turns 0 o'clock, adult time!
だっだっだめですか？フリルの服着たら
Is-is-is that no good? If I wear frilly clothes,
だっだっだて魔法少女になってみたい！
i-i-I want to try becoming a magical girl!
少女無罪 レクイエム
Girl innocent, Requiem.
なんだってするから見ないでキミたち
I'll do anything, so don't look at me you guys!
ちょっと覗いてみたい ああ...我慢にイジってさ
I want to take a little peek. Ah... teasing with patience,
女子ゴコロも本気にしちゃう
making a girl's heart serious too!
嵐の中も一緒に、行こう？
Even through the storm, shall we go together?
ハートにチャーム 美少女無罪 あれあれどうした？
Charm on the heart, bishoujo innocent, hey hey what's wrong?
めんどくさいようなんて言っちゃって かまってくれるキミが好き
Saying things like "how annoying" - I love the you who pays attention to me!
ド・キ・ド・キ・して rouge?
Do-ki-do-ki-shi-te rouge?
やさしくしてね17才
Be gentle with me, I'm 17 years old!
突っ込んでけ！検地を楽しまんちょ？
Charge right in! Enjoying the inspection, huh?
ドキドキして…ウーイ！
Heart pounding... Uii!
あ、よろしくね！
Ah, nice to meet you!
このウーイの魅力、魔力、深奥力
This Uii's charm, magic, and profound power
キミの女ね♡
You're my woman♡
この船内って 捕まっていて
Stay trapped inside this ship,
世界の厳しさ 見せてあげるから！
I'll show you the vastness of the world!
出航──！！
Set sail──!!
キュートは正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice, beautiful girl innocence,
キミの一番目指して ヨークソロロー！
Aiming to be your number one, yo-heave-ho!
冗談ばっか好きだけど真剣よ
I love joking around, but I'm serious!
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん きゅっ きゅっ きゅるんるん
Kyu kyu kyurun, kyu kyu kyurunrun,
恋する気持ち 17才
A girl in love at 17 years old,
0時にはなっちゃうわ オトナの時間
Turning 12 at midnight, grown-up time!
ド・キ・ド・キ・して rouge?
Do-ki-do-ki-shi-te rouge?
まだ早い♡
Still too early♡
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！マリン！マリン！
Innocent! Innocent! Beautiful girl innocence! Marine! Marine!
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！ウーイ！ウーイ！
Innocent! Innocent! Beautiful girl innocence! Uii! Uii!
ウーイは無罪！ マリン船長とウーイちゃおー！
Uii is innocent! Captain Marine and Uii-chao!
うーいちゃおー！
Uii-chao!
マリンじゃあ！あ、うーいじゃあ！
Marine-ja! Ah, Uii-ja!
ということで、はー、疲れてるー！
And with that, phew, I'm so tired!
ええ、すごくさすが9歳、元気いっぱいじゃん。
Eh, as expected of a 9-year-old, so full of energy.
ちょっと無理してる。
Pushing yourself a bit, huh.
はい、マリンの急、急所です、すいません。
Yes, Marine's weak point... sorry.
前も9歳ではない！
I wasn't 9 back then either!
そうです、ないの7周年ライブにじゃん、うーいちゃんが来てくれました！
That's right, Uii-chan came to Marine's 7th anniversary live!
イェーイ！お邪魔しまーす！おめでとう！
Yay! Sorry to interrupt! Congratulations!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
なんとね、マリンね、16歳のうーいとはね、うん、まあもうめちゃ、マブ？
You know, Marine and 16-year-old Uii are, yeah, pretty much besties?
あ、そうなんだ。
Oh, is that so.
なんだけどね、うーいちゃんともね、これからマブになっていきたいなって思ってて、初絡みなんだけどね。
But you know, I was hoping to become besties with Uii-chan too from now on, even though this is our first interaction.
どうぞよろしく。あ、帰ります。
Please treat me well. Ah, I'm heading home.
ちょ、ちょ、待てよ！ちょ、待てよ！ちょ、待てよ！
Wait, wait, hold on! Hold on! Hold on!
ということでね、はい、うーいちゃん、何か気づかない？
So anyway, yes, Uii-chan, do you notice anything?
え？露出？
Eh? Exposure?
お、あ、興味ある？興味ある？
Oh, ah, interested? Interested?
これね、うーいちゃん、あなたのはなったウービームだ！
This, Uii-chan, is the Uii beam you unleashed!
あの、新しい衣装ってさ、聞いてください。
Um, about the new outfit, please listen.
ウービームで服のはじけとんだ、そんなのあるわけなーい！
The edge of the clothes blown off by the Uii beam—there's no such thing!
っていう感じでね、これし衣装となっています。
And so, that's what this outfit is.
え、てか、ばん、乗り遅れみ付いてない？え、そうなの？付いてるの？
Eh, wait, are you missing out? Eh, is that right? Is it attached?
欲しい！一個もらっていい？
I want it! Can I have one?
うわ、すごい9歳っぽい。めっちゃ可愛い。いいよ、ぶち。
Whoa, so 9-year-old like. Super cute. Sure, Buchi.
おっぱい曲げる、ぶち。お土産。じゃあね、じゃあ待てよ！
Bending boobs, Buchi. Souvenir. Hey, wait!
ちょ、待てよ！ちょ、待てよ！見てほら、ここにさ、
Hey, wait! Hey, wait! Look, see, right here,
ほら、3、3。あ、本当だ！背中に3
see, 3, 3. Oh, truly! A 3 on the back!
ほら、おしりすっけ！30じゃないよ！
Look, see-through butt! Not 30!
3年！30じゃないよ！
3 years! Not 30!
いや、うーいちゃんね、これね、まだまだ脱げるんで、大丈夫ですか？
No, Uii-chan, you know, this still comes off more, is that alright?
この後ね、これから、ユーチューバーとして大丈夫ですか？
After this, as a YouTuber, will that be alright?
髪型とか、服とか、まだまだね、違うのがあるのでね、みんなね、これに満足して帰らないように
Hairstyle, clothes, there's still more different ones, so everyone don't go home satisfied with just this,
、みんな頑張って隠してください。まだまだあるよ、まだまだあるよ。
everyone please hide it. There's still more, there's still more.
ということで、初選曲の話もしようと思うんですけど、
So, I also want to talk about our first song choice,
ええ、うーいと、あ、じゃ、うーいちゃん、うーいちゃんとは、
Uh, Uii and, ah, Uii-chan, Uii-chan and,
ええ、もやっぱりね、持ち歌のロリ神でレクイエム！
uh, well, as expected, singing the theme song 'Loli Kami Requiem!'
やりましたけど、可愛い。
We did it, so cute.
どうでしたか？ええね、マリンも歌みたも出してるんですけど、
How was it? Um, Marine also released a cover song version,
九体ね、そう、マリンの歌みたのバージョンだとめっちゃ、
Nine-body, right, in Marine's cover version it's super,
レ・ク・イ・エ・ム！って感じで歌ってねじり出してたんだけど、
Requiem! like that, twisting it out,
ま、今回はね、もうなんかマリンもこのさ、姿のまま「レクイエム！」って言ったらちょっと、あっ！となるから、
Well, this time, if Marine says "Requiem!" in this exact appearance, it'll be a bit like, ah!
言ってるね、もう今ね。そこは、ちょっと真面目にね、普通にいつものマリンで
You're saying it already now. That part, a bit seriously, normally as usual Marine
歌わさせていただきました。そっちの方がいいよ。
sang it. That's better.
あ、マリンちゃん、なんだよ。
Ah, Marine-chan, what.
なんでもない。お家族りしないほうがいいよ。やめて、やめて。
It's nothing. You shouldn't make a family. Stop, stop.
あ、それは、あの、うーいの方とはね、Kアリーナで、
Ah, that is, um, with Uii's side, at K-Arena,
うーいのライブで一緒に歌わせてもらった、その時ね、歌えましたので、
at Uii's live, we got to sing together, at that time we sang it, so
疲れた。
I'm tired.
疲れた、疲れたでしょ。いいよ、もう帰って、疲れたでしょ。じゃ、帰りましょ。
Tired, you must be tired. Alright, go home already, you're tired, right. Well, let's head back.
まだまだライブは続くぞ！ 冷たい！ まだまだ続く！
The live continues! It's cold! It still continues!
レッツゴー！ え、そんなに求められてないことあるの？
Let's go! Eh, is there really not that much demand for this?
パレード パレード パレード！
Parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ
It's time to shine!
呼び合う声を 合図に
With our calling voices as the signal,
パレード パレード パレード！
parade, parade, parade!
探しにいく スタートは 何度だって
We'll go search—no matter how many times we restart!
手を上げて Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Raise your hands, clap your hands across the sea!
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, may the sound reach!
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands!
ほら 一緒に Everybody
C'mon now, together, everybody!
Clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Clap your hands, across the sky!
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, may the claps resound!
手を叩こう 手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands!
光り差す 僕たちの未来
Light illuminates our future!
コソコソコソ？
Kon kon kon?
Yes こんな狐に化かされて
Yes, fooled by such a fox,
Knock, knock, knock 心を開いて
knock, knock, knock, open your heart!
everything's gonna be alrightって感じよ
Everything's gonna be alright, they say,
今、噂の bewitch you
now bewitching you with rumors!
コンコンコン
Kon kon kon!
Yes こんな狐に化かされて
Yes, fooled by such a fox,
Knock, knock, knock 心を開いて
knock, knock, knock, open your heart!
everything's gonna be alrightって感じよ
Everything's gonna be alright, they say,
今、宇宙の真ん中チューニング
tuning right in the middle of the universe!
コンコンコン 魔法をかけて
Kon kon kon, casting a spell,
飽きるまで be with you
until we're tired, be with you!
もっと好きになってもらいたいのか
I want you to love me even more!
頭の中は君ばっかでよかった
My head is full of you, isn't that nice?
突っ放すなんて向いてないでさ もう休み時間はちゃわ
Don't act so cold to me, recess is over already!
ずっとずっと好きがいいの
I want to keep liking you forever and ever!
心の奥もっと決め打ち 乙女心に
Deep down in my heart, make up your mind with a maiden's spirit!
こっち向いててよねタニ アモ もう離さないから
Look this way, honey, I won't let you go anymore!
世界に ラブユー オーオーオー
To the world, I love you!
ラブユー ラブユー オーオーオー
Love you, love you!
つまらないデイズもう散々ね！
Boring days are already done for!
奇跡願っているだけの人生
A life just wishing for miracles,
watch me do-do-do-do-do 呪術秘中トリック無しのマジック
watch me do-do-do-do-do, magic without tricks or secrets!
I wanna be free! だってまだ序盤でしょ？
I wanna be free! Because we're still just starting out, right?
ビビデバビビデブーわ ビビデバビビデブーわ
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boowa, bibbidi-bobbidi-boowa!
どうせ後戻りはしょうがないからシュートを撃つくらい
Since there's no turning back anyway, might as well take the shot!
ビビデバビビデブーわ ビビデバビビデブーわ
Bibbidi-bobbidi-boowa, bibbidi-bobbidi-boowa!
ヤバい明日となれば七転び八起きでしょう
Even if tomorrow's crazy, it's fall down seven times, stand up eight!
失礼しますが死んでください！
Excuse me, but please die!
kill 'em with the bass 殺す事が楽しい
Kill 'em with the bass, murder is so fun!
teehee bitch murder is so fucking 可愛い
Teehee bitch, murder is so fucking cute!
死神先生 Calliope
Reaper-sensei Calliope,
kill 'em with the bass 'til we get 'em to say alright
" yay ! 素敵な暗殺 ~ " so it goes dead beats listen up
"Yay, what a lovely assassination~" so it goes, dead beats listen up!
取引中シネマティック
Cinematic in the middle of a trade,
murder's anyway 'cause it's human nature
申し訳ないですやり過ぎました
My apologies, I went way too far!
一体全体任された ドキドキゴッド
Entrusted entirely, the doggy god's street!
you can go by bye byebye baby
You can go by-bye byebye baby!
当然今日のシップドド ドキドキゴッド
Naturally today's ship-dodo, doggy doggy god!
clap your hands wag your tail on and on and on
バタバタ震えるこの既存パンク
Flapping and shaking, this conventional punk,
砕んだら放さない ワンチャンスで輝く
once we grasp it we won't let go, shining on one chance!
ドキドキゴッド
Doggy god!
あ
あことじょうほーかたのレストランで
Ah, at an information-overload restaurant,
嘘っぱちのメニューにお茶をこぼして
spilling tea on a bogus menu!
君とモグモグ モグモグ 追撃戦のなかでモグモグ
Mogu mogu with you, mogu mogu in the middle of a chase!
全身を払ってこの群れ 満足に
Brushing off my whole body, satisfying this flock,
なる未来を願っているよモグモグ
wishing for a future where we're full!
モグモグYUMMY! まじカミング
Mogu mogu YUMMY! Magic coming,
ヨムヨムありのままで
yom yom just as we are!
モグモグYUMMY! まじカミング
Mogu mogu YUMMY! Magic coming,
このよ味わうんだ うまうま
tasting this world, yum yum!
魅惑を隠す箱 秘宝に香る危険な
The box hiding allure, the dangerous fragrance of treasure...
ドキドキしてrouge？
Pounding, pounding, playing rouge?
いきますよ〜！
Here we go~!
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！
Innocent! Innocent! Bishoujo innocent!
マリン！マリン！マリンは無罪！
Marine! Marine! Marine is innocent!
やっぱりキラキラもっとクラクラ
Still sparkling, even more dizzying!
ねえ、言ったよね？年齢なんて関係ないってさ
Hey, you said it, right? That age doesn't matter at all,
そういうめんどくさいのも含めて愛してくれるって
and that you'd love me even with all that troublesome stuff...
ふーんどぅ、そういうこというんだ。
Hmph, so that's how it is.
ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますけど？
By the way, in this ship, bishoujo innocence applies, you know?
まかせて！魔法で若返り
Leave it to me! Reversing age with magic,
ヒミツの素顔はキミにだけ
my secret true face is just for you!
トクベツですよ〜！？
It's special, okay~?!
ah…アタシ厄介よ
Ah... I'm a handful.
ah…港になんじゃ
Ah... What kind of port is this?
はしゃげないわ近頃は
Can't get too excited lately,
宝の島にしてほしい気分
feeling like I want a treasure island!
出航ーー！！
Set sail--!!
キュートは正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice, bishoujo innocence!
キミの一番目指してよーそろー！
Aiming to be your number one, yosoro!
本当は自信ないけど頑張っちゃう
Though I'm not confident, I'll do my best!
ahoy！！
Ahoy!!
きゅっきゅっきゅるん きゅっきゅっきゅるるん
Kyu-kyu-kyu-run, kyu-kyu-kyu-rurun!
恋する気持ち17歳
Feeling of love, 17 years old!
0時（てっぺん）になっちゃうオトナの時間
When it turns midnight, adult time begins!
やっぱりキラキラもっとクラクラ
Still sparkling, even more dizzying!
ド・キ・ド・キ・して rouge？
Do-ki-do-ki-shite rouge?
まだ早い♡
Still too early♡
だ、だ、だめですかっ？
Is that not allowed?
フリルの服装着たら
If I wear ruffled clothes—
そんなこと、ないよ
That's not true—
だ、だ、だ、だ、で
Da, da, da, da, de—
魔法少女になってみたい
I want to become a magical girl!
ギルギル有罪！？
Guilty, guilty?!
進路はナンナン星
Our course is Planet Nannan!
ちょっぴり足んない積極性？
Just a little lacking in proactiveness?
同じ未来を見ていたい あの夢手にしたい
Wanting to see the same future, wanting to hold that dream in our hands!
それぞれ違ったココロで走れgo
Running with our respective hearts, go!
どこを見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えていた
In a pitch-black place where a tiny hope sprouted,
ほんの小さな希望にこの瞳奪われていた
these eyes were captivated by it.
不安で揺らぐ心をうまくチューニングして
Tuning our trembling hearts with anxiety,
ほんの小さな勇気を振り絞っていたよ
summoning a tiny bit of courage.
諦めの文字 デリートして進む
The word "give up" deleted, we move forward!
苦しいときも もう私はひとりじゃないから
Even in painful times, I'm no longer alone anymore,
だからもっと夢追いかけたい
so I want to chase my dreams even more!
ワクワク止まらない 想像越えてく
The excitement doesn't stop, surpassing imagination,
世界見せてあげる アクセスしてみたい
I'll show you the world, I want to access it!
後悔なんてそうさせない
I won't let you have any regrets!
それぞれ違ったココロで走れgo
Running with our respective hearts, go!
仮想の空に輝く 眩しい想いは
Shining in the virtual sky, this dazzling feeling
見たことのない光を 現実に届けるよ
delivers an unseen light into reality!
いつも聴こえるエールは ここにキャプチャーして
Catching the cheers we always hear right here,
また新しい光を 探したくなるよ
it makes us want to search for a new light!
君の笑顔は 保存して進む
Saving your smile, we move forward,
悲しいときに 見返すよ力が湧くから
looking back when sad, because it gives us strength!
胸を張って夢追いかけたい
Wanting to chase dreams with pride,
奇跡の物語 一緒に作ろう
let's create a miraculous story together!
終わらない夢を 誰一人欠かせない
An endless dream, without leaving a single person behind,
愛が舞ったこの世界
in this world where love dances!
はーい注目！まあいいちょっ踊ってこうか？
Haa-i, attention! Well, why not dance a little bit?
視線牛耳ってんのは... Ⅲ
What's grabbing everyone's gaze is... III
our night's just begun aye , let's blast it !
Our night's just begun, aye, let's blast it!
赤く照るface ヒートアップしちゃって light up the place
Red-lit face, heating up, light up the place!
渇いた喉潤すオアシスさ マリンブルー ah-ha！
An oasis quenching a thirsty throat, marine blue, ah-ha!
たまらないんだろ? from shore to shore i'm gonna get your ass on the dance floor
Can't get enough, from shore to shore I'm gonna get your ass on the dance floor!
we 're taking over l . a . , miami , new york
We're taking over L.A., Miami, New York,
a slave to the rhythm and you 're ready for more
a slave to the rhythm and you're ready for more.
if you wanna block my shine ? go get your sunblock
If you wanna block my shine? Go get your sunblock,
i can make it rain when i hit the jackpot
baby , get ready if you wanna ride on with the ogs
Baby, get ready if you wanna ride on with the OGs.
アー ウチチ な 二人は だあれ？
Who are these two chummy people?
hands up ぶち上げ たまえ！
Hands up, put 'em in the air!
クラっときちゃう様な 熱が足りない
The heat making us dizzy is not enough,
our night's just begun aye let 's blast it !
our night's just begun, aye, let's blast it!
はじけて派手にいったーれ！ 来世まで
Burst out and go all out! Until the afterlife,
we wanna party all eyes on me i can taste the high aye
まだまだ沸いてこうぜ
let's keep heating up!
はーい注目！まあいいちょっ踊ってこうか？
Haa-i, attention! Well, why not dance a little bit?
視線牛耳ってんのは... Ⅲ
What's grabbing everyone's gaze is... III
she got the gyatt now let me see you work with all of that ( ah ! )
She got the gyatt, now let me see you work with all of that (ah!)
can you call a doctor 'cause this baddie 's giving me a heart attack
Can you call a doctor 'cause this baddie's giving me a heart attack?
but you know what 's scary to me
But you know what's scary to me?
holo make girls look like halle barry to me
Holo makes girls look like Halle Berry to me.
i 'm - 2 bars from being canceled so l gotta leave you ever so carefully ( ah ! )
I'm 2 bars from being canceled, so I gotta leave you ever so carefully (ah!)
bring in the heat that can't be splashed away
fishing a big catch , the stardom i deserve
fishing a big catch, the stardom I deserve.
but i 'm just chilling courvoisier , i 'm sipping 'cause i got that juice
But I'm just chilling, Courvoisier, I'm sipping 'cause I got that juice,
and i might let you have a taste
この身体で let me rock your body
Let me rock your body with this body,
秘宝な素肌に now put that camera on me
now put that camera on my treasured skin!
beside a bonfire our luring smoke takes you higher
ね？ we drive you crazy ahoy
right? We drive you crazy, ahoy!
熱苦しくなってこうもうどうしようもない my bright spotlight
Getting intensely passionate, nothing we can do, my bright spotlight,
どんどん新境地いっちゃいそう? (oh baby)
getting ever closer to new frontiers? (oh baby)
アー ウチチ な 二人は だあれ？
Who are these two chummy people?
hands up ぶち上げ たまえ！
Hands up, put 'em in the air!
クラっときちゃう様な 熱が足りない
The heat making us dizzy is not enough,
our night's just begun aye let 's blast it !
our night's just begun, aye, let's blast it!
はじけて派手にいったーれ！ 来世まで
Burst out and go all out! Until the afterlife,
we wanna party all eyes on me i can taste the high aye
まだまだ沸いてこうぜ
let's keep heating up!
はーい注目！まあいいちょっ踊ってこうか？
Haa-i, attention! Well, why not dance a little bit?
視線牛耳ってんのは...
What's grabbing everyone's gaze is...
bring it back , let 's hit it one last time !
Bring it back, let's hit it one last time!
aye 俺らさぁ、マジで最強じゃん？
Aye, aren't we seriously the strongest?
just two besties so fly !
Just two besties so fly!
息つく暇もないほど
With no time to even catch my breath,
温い退屈な夜道でmellow mellow mellow
down the lukewarm, boring night road, mellow mellow mellow
ルールは無視して行きたいんだね
You want to break the rules and go, right?
So burn my burn my heart
uh 悟られそう
Uh, looks like you'll be found out
uh 可か不可か
Uh, pass or fail?
Get down now
uh あーあもうきっと 優等ぶったいじゃ居られないくらいどうしようもないや yuh
You can't act like an honor student anymore, there's nothing we can do, yuh
無理目のクエストちゃんha
An impossible quest, ha
実存? フィクション?
Existence? Fiction?
You make me サゲなんなのさ?
You make me feel down, what is this?
I know the way
願ってるばっかじゃ叶わない
Just wishing won't make it come true
めちゃくちゃにされたって変わらない
Even if it gets all messed up, it won't change
まあね 噛み奪え 覚醒 Find the way
Well, bite and steal it, awaken, Find the way
待ってライト浴びる感覚 甘い罠
Wait, the feeling of bathing in lights, a sweet trap
見当違いdisも聞き飽きたわ
I'm sick of hearing misguided disses too
そりゃいけないところまで Take me higher
Take me higher to places I shouldn't go
どう? Turning back 無理ってとっくに分かってんでしょ
You've known it's impossible all along
終わらない夢を描こう 描いて
Let's paint an endless dream, paint it
願ったまま欲しがったその先へ
Toward beyond what we wished and desired
終わらない夜を超えていこう 超えていこうこのまま 焦がれた向こう側へ
Let's go beyond an endless night to the other side we longed for
はあぶっちぎれ解せないや 勝算なくても行っちゃえ!とかな
Completely outrun it, it doesn't make sense without winning odds!
運命感じる感受性は否めない ウチら負けない
You can't deny the feeling of destiny, we won't lose
跳べ 吠え 目で 追って
Jump, howl, watch, chase
いつでもNO.1そこだけ 速攻
Always NO.1, right there, blitz
揺らげ 攻め 甘美な時
Sway, attack, sweet time
Ride on now
Shake it up, まだまだ
Shake it up, still more
Go beyond the way! yuh
終わらない夢を描こう 描いて
Let's paint an endless dream, paint it
願ったまま欲しがったその先へ
Toward beyond what we wished and desired
終わらない夜を超えていこう 超えていこうこのまま 焦がれた向こう側へ
Let's go beyond an endless night to the other side we longed for
はあぶっちぎれ解せないや 勝算なくても行っちゃえ!とかな
Completely outrun it, it doesn't make sense without winning odds!
運命感じる感受性は否めない ウチら負けない
You can't deny the feeling of destiny, we won't lose
跳べ 吠え 目で 追って
Jump, howl, watch, chase
いつでもNO.1そこだけ 速攻
Always NO.1, right there, blitz
揺らげ 攻め 甘美な時
Sway, attack, sweet time
Ride on now
Shake it up, まだまだ
Shake it up, still more
Go beyond the way! yuh
uh 悟られそう
Uh, looks like you'll be found out
uh 可か不可か
Uh, pass or fail?
Get down now
uh あーあもうきっと優等ぶったいじゃ居られないくらいどうしようもないや yuh
I'm sure you can't act like an honor student anymore, yuh
無理目のクエストちゃんha
An impossible quest, ha
実存? フィクション?
Existence? Fiction?
You make me サゲなんなのさ?
You make me feel down, what is this?
I know the way
Bring in the hits that count
Dissolve away
Wishing away
Cat-walk oddities
Our hearts are beating
I'm just chillin'
Don't fuss here
On step ahead
'Cause I can bet you
choose
the best
Let you have a taste
この身体で
with this body,
Let me lock your body
光放つ裸に
into a glowing nakedness
Sirens on fire, all o-rings fall down
Step to the rhythm and ready for more!
If you want to rock my shine, then catch your solo, hun!
熱く熱くなってこう
Let's get hotter and hotter
もうどうしょうもない
There's nothing more we can do
無理目のクエストちゃんha
An impossible quest, ha
実存? フィクション?
Existence? Fiction?
You make me サゲなんなのさ?
You make me feel down, what is this?
I know the way
願ってるばっかじゃ叶わない
Just wishing won't make it come true
めちゃくちゃにされたって変わらない
Even if it gets all messed up, it won't change
まあね 噛み奪え 覚醒 Find the way
Well, bite and steal it, awaken, Find the way
待ってライト浴びる感覚 甘い罠
Wait, the feeling of bathing in lights, a sweet trap
見当違いdisも聞き飽きたわ
I'm sick of hearing misguided disses too
そりゃいけないところまで Take me higher
Take me higher to places I shouldn't go
どう? Turning back 無理ってとっくに分かってんでしょ
You've known it's impossible all along
終わらない夢を描こう 描いて
Let's paint an endless dream, paint it
願ったまま欲しがったその先へ
Toward beyond what we wished and desired
終わらない夜を超えていこう 超えていこうこのまま 焦がれた向こう側へ
Let's go beyond an endless night to the other side we longed for
はあぶっちぎれ解せないや 勝算なくても行っちゃえ!とかな
Completely outrun it, it doesn't make sense without winning odds!
運命感じる感受性は否めない ウチら負けない
You can't deny the feeling of destiny, we won't lose
跳べ 吠え 目で 追って
Jump, howl, watch, chase
いつでもNO.1そこだけ 速攻
Always NO.1, right there, blitz
揺らげ 攻め 甘美な時
Sway, attack, sweet time
Ride on now
Shake it up, まだまだ
Shake it up, still more
Go beyond the way! yuh
IRIS OUT
[Title: IRIS OUT]
ダメダメダメ 脳みその中からやめろ
No, no, no, stop it from inside your brain
バカとはめくもられで
you idiots wrapped in folly,
Darling baby darling
琥珀の羅針盤ときめきゆきあしたスピロソフィ
amber compass, fluttering heartbeat, tomorrow's philosophy,
死のほどかいはめづかい 何がしょうに触れるくらい
biting so hard it hurts, how much touches your soul?
風のクラシック 気付けば閉じこの様に生まれた君が笑い
A wind classic, before you know it, closed in like this, you born into this world smile
たらと心臓いきのえはらばらなるわ
and your beating heart scatters and breaks apart,
頭とこの心臓 拾う脈で I love you
head and this heart, picking up the pulse, I love you,
IRIS OUT いっそどうしよう この思いをどうしよう
IRIS OUT, what should we do with this feeling?
暴れの空の 皿目が溶けてからになりそうさ
The stormy sky's... melting into emptiness,
ドンコ 立ち上がって 終わりにしよう
Don't go, stand up, let's end this,
震えて 笑い合おうよ
shivering, let's smile together.
今この世でキミだけ大正解
In this world right now, only you are the absolute right answer!
だれ だれ だれ だれ...
Who, who, who, who...?
引っくり返す価値もない キミだけルールは例外
There's no point in turning it over, only your rules are the exception.
イスとモースルは殺せない 稼ぎ放題
Chairs and morsels can't be killed, unlimited earnings!
キミが選んだアッパーデッキで デッコにスチグマ申訳ねえな
On the upper deck you chose, my apologies for the stigma on deck.
譲らして 抜き取って 心着て
Surrendering, extracting, wearing my heart.
死ぬほど可愛いウマミづけ 何が至福に浸るくらい
So painfully cute and flavorful, enough to soak in bliss.
枕乱し気付けば当人 この世に生まれたキミが悪い
Disturbing pillows, before you know it, you're the one born into this world.
パチモンでもいい何でもいい 今キミと夏いてる全て欲しい
Knockoffs are fine, anything is fine, I want everything summering with you now.
頚動脈から愛ラブヒューズ吹き出せ
Let love fuses burst out from your carotid artery!
Ayris out!
一体どうしよう この想いどうしよう 阿鼻叫喚
What on earth should I do? What about this feeling? Pandemonium!
サロメが溶けてケロリになりそう
Salome is melting, about to become nonchalant.
バッチ開いておごれチリソー
Open your batch and treat me to some chili sauce.
今この世でキミだけ大正解
In this world right now, only you are the absolute right answer!
だれ だれ だれ だれ...
Who, who, who, who...?
Ayris out!
ピカタ カボ おめでとう！
Pikata Kobo, congratulations!
ありがと カボ！
Thank you Kobo!
Yeah, Happy Anniversary!
そうそうそうそう、7th！
That's right, 7th!
かわいー、かわいー！はい。
So cute, so cute! Yes.
ちょっとフード似てるよ、ほら、ね？似てるね？
Our hoods look kind of similar, see? Don't they?
似てる、似てる、ほら、ふー…あ、これフード。
They do, they do, see, hu... ah, this is the hood.
どう？フード？
How is it? A hood?
こぼもフード、ありますよ。え？
Kobo has a hood too, you know. Eh?
これ？どれ？どこや？
This? Which one? Where is it?
埋まってる！そう！かぶれないだろ、それ！
It's buried! That's right! You can't put that on!
わ、かわいいね！
Ah, how cute!
え、ど、どこが可愛い？
Eh, wh-where is it cute?
え、じゃ、セクシーな、お、スイムスーツ、でしょ？
Well, the sexy, um, swimsuit, right?
あ、スイムスーツ！あー、セクシー！
Ah, the swimsuit! Ah, so sexy!
水着可愛いよ、こぼも！このスイムスーツ欲しい！
The swimsuit is cute, Kobo wants this too!
あ、欲しい？うん、なんか、
Ah, you want it? Yeah, somehow,
こぼは、リボン好き！
Kobo loves ribbons!
リボン？どのリボン？この、いや、みた…あー！リボンは、これ！
Ribbon? Which ribbon? This, no, wait... Ah! The ribbon is this!
これ？うん、ち、さいけど。あ、ちっちゃいリボン、ちっちゃいリボン。
This? Yeah, it's sm-small though. Ah, a tiny ribbon, a tiny ribbon.
あ、みた…あ、みた、みた、あ、ほんとだ！きれい！
Ah, wait... Ah, look, look, ah, really! Beautiful!
あ、すごい！あ、こっちも？あ、こっちも？
Ah, amazing! Ah, over here too? Over here too?
あ、そうそうそう！これ！
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah! This!
え、めっちゃ可愛い！このリボンが、わあ！あ…待って、リボンとお尻どっちが可愛い？
Eh, super cute! This ribbon is, wow! Wait, which is cuter, the ribbon or the butt?
もっと、もっとセク…もっとセクシーに…！おい！おい！おい！
More, more se-more sexy...! Hey! Hey! Hey!
うわ！うわ！うわ！助かる！
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Godsend!
え、こぼもっとさ、脱いでるの観たいでしょ？
Hey Kobo, you want to see me more undressed, right?
あ、あの、これ、ぱっ…え、だめだよ！
Ah, um, this, pa... Eh, you can't do that!
だめ？うまいうまい、脱いで脱いでくる！え？見せてあげる、こぼ。
No good? Smooth, smooth, I'll take it off and come back! Eh? I'll show you, Kobo.
え？大丈夫ですか？楽しみにしてて！
Eh? Are you okay with this? Look forward to it!
え？やべえ！やべえ！こぼ見て！やべえ！こぼ見て！
Eh? Oh crap! Oh crap! Kobo look! Oh crap! Kobo look!
わあ！わあ！わあ！セクシーレディ！わあ、チル！
Wow! Wow! Wow! Sexy lady! Wow, chill!
もいもい、いいよ、服着るよ。服着る、やべえ！
Moi moi, okay, I'll put my clothes on. Putting them on, oh crap!
ダンスれないようにね！やべえ、子ども…子どもの、どんぐ…あ、もう来た、もう来た、ほら！じゃあ！
So you can't dance! Oh crap, children's... acorn... ah, it's already here, look! So!
ああ、大丈夫！あ、これセーフ、セーフ！セーフ！あ、すごーい！
Ah, it's okay! Ah, this is safe, safe! Safe! Ah, amazing!
で、今日はね、あの、あいやいやのね、そう、楽しかった！楽しかった！
And today, um, about 'I I I', yeah, it was so fun! So fun!
お、マリンのお尻……
Oh, Marine's butt...
And I like it, oh, today, I, I, I, is just since…
そうなの、すっごいかっこいいバージョンをね、曲をもらって、え、カバーさせてもらいました！
That's right, we got this super cool version of the song and got to cover it!
かっこいいバージョン、ありがとうございます！ Great job with the cover.
Thank you for the cool version! Great job with the cover.
ねぇ、マリーの英語のラップどうだった？シガットキャ、ノルミソー、ウォークイットオールアラウダ！
Hey, how was Marine's English rap? 'She got cat, no remi so, walk it all alouda!'
シガットキャット！シガットキャット！キャット、ゲット、イェー！
She got cat! She got cat! Cat, get, yeah!
Now let me see you work with all of that. うまっ！ちょっと待って…ま、うまっ、かま！
Now let me see you work with all of that. Smooth! Wait a sec... smooth, kama!
え、で、何？ノルミソー、ウォークイットオールアラウダ？それは英語ですか？
Eh, so what was that? 'No remi so, walk it all alouda?' Is that English?
英語です！
It's English!
えっと、なりぐりっしゅです！ Can you call a doctor?
Umm, it's Nariglish! Can you call a doctor?
こづば、またな！えらいえらい、がんばったな！
Kozuba, see you again! Good job, you worked hard!
英語！うん、がんばった！やったー！
English! Yeah, I worked hard! Yay!
続きますので、ぜひ見ていってください！
As it continues, please be sure to keep watching!
いやこんばんは！ありがと！
Hey, good evening! Thank you!
重いやった
So heavy!
死んだ
I'm dead.
お別れしたのはもっと 前のことだったような
It seems like we said goodbye a bit longer ago than that
悲しい光は封じ込めて 踵すり減らしたんだ
I locked away the sad light and wore down my heels
君といた時は見えた 今は見えなくなった
I could see it when I was with you, but now I can't see it anymore
透明な流星をぼんやりと でもそれだけでも探している
Looking dimly for a transparent shooting star, but even just for that
しょっちゅう歌を歌ったよ その時だけのメロディーを
I often sang songs, melodies just for those moments
寂しくなんかなかったよ ちゃんと寂しくなれたから
I wasn't lonely, because I was able to feel lonely properly
いつまでどこまでなんて 正常か異常かなんて
Until when, where, whether it's normal or abnormal
考える暇もないほど歩くのは大変だ
It's so hard to walk that I don't even have time to think about it
理想で作った道を 現実が塗り替えていくよ
Reality is overwriting the path made by ideals
思い出はその軌道上で 輝きになって残っている
Memories remain as brilliance along that orbit
お別れしたのは何で 何のためだったんだろうな
I wonder why and for what purpose we said goodbye
悲しい光が僕の影を 前に長く伸ばしている
The sad light stretches my shadow far ahead
時々熱があるよ 時間がある時眠るよ
Sometimes I have a fever, I sleep when I have time
夢だと解るその中で 君と会ってからまた行こう
In that dream where I know it's a dream, I'll meet you and go again
晴天とはほど遠い 終わらない闇にも
Even in the endless darkness, far from clear skies
星を思い浮かべたなら すぐ銀河の中だ
If I conjure up the stars, I'm right in the galaxy
あまり泣かなくなっても 靴を新しくしても
Even if I don't cry much anymore, even if I get new shoes
大丈夫 あの痛みは 忘れたって消やしない
It's alright, that pain won't disappear even if you forget it
伝えたいことが きっとあったんだろうな
There must have been something I wanted to convey
恐らくありきたりなんだろうけど こんなにも
It's probably cliché, but never like this
お別れしたことは 出会ったことと繋がっている
What we said goodbye to is connected to what we met
あの透明な水星は 透明だから無くならない
That transparent Mercury won't disappear because it's transparent
丸の数三角どれかなんて 皆と比べてどうかなんて
Whether it's circles, triangles, how it compares to everyone
確かめる間もないほど生きるのは最高だ
Living without even time to check is the best
あまり泣かなくなっても ごまかして笑っていくよ
Even if I don't cry much anymore, I'll just fake it and smile
大丈夫 あの痛みは 忘れたって消やしない
It's alright, that pain won't disappear even if you forget it
暖かなことがきと あったんだろうな
There must have been warmth for sure
おそらくありきたりなんだろうけど こんなにも
It's probably cliché, but never like this
大丈夫 この光の 始まりには君がいる
It's alright, you are at the beginning of this light
私は、わたしの事が好き。
I love who I am.
朝起きて今天是何しよう
Waking up, what should I do today?
好奇心抑えらんない
I can't contain my curiosity!
踊り出すあとは制御不能
Once I start dancing, there's no stopping me!
テンプレは丸めて捨てて
Crumple up the template and throw it away,
スキップで吹き飛ばしちゃお
and blow it away with a skip!
地球全部塗り替えっちゃお
Let's repaint the entire Earth!
カチコチはだるいし無理！
Being stiff is tedious, no way!
まだ無理！
Still no way!
そんなソッコ―イチ抜け！
Quick escape from that!
あっかんべーなんだが上等！
Teasingly sticking out my tongue, bring it on!
心拍数上げて生きようよ
Let's live with our hearts racing!
退屈奪っていこうよ
Let's steal away the boredom!
ウザいのも
Even annoying things,
沼って好きになっちゃうよ
get obsessed and grow to love them!
完璧キャラ無理ゲー知らんぷり
Acting like a perfect character is an impossible game,
可愛すぎちゃってグランプリ
I'll play dumb. Too cute, grand prix!
Ah 何でも知りたい 味わいしたい
Ah, I want to know everything, I want to taste it!
誰も止められないし
Nobody can stop me,
歌わずにはいられない
And I can't help but sing!
もしも手遅れ諦めるより
Rather than giving up too late,
もしもベットかましたい
I want to make a big bet!
この世界知らない方が損じゃん？
Aren't you losing out if you don't know this world?
知らない方が損じゃん？
Aren't you losing out?
疲れたらちょっとサボって
When you're tired, slack off a bit,
当分で回復して
Recover for a while,
自分のご機嫌取ろう
And keep your own mood up!
優等生演じてても無理！
Acting like an honor student is impossible!
演じてても無理！
Even acting like it is impossible!
ナチュラルで愛しい女の子なんだが
I'm a natural, lovely girl, but—
なんだが
But!
最強！大好き囲まれて生きようよ
The strongest! Let's live surrounded by what we love!
大好き囲まれて生きようよ
Let's live surrounded by love!
明日も笑ってたいよ
I want to keep smiling tomorrow too!
知っちゃったら
Once you know it,
そのまま好きになっちゃうぜ
You'll just fall in love with it as is!
妄想今日さえ抜け出して
Break out of even today's delusions,
頂上にだって連れてって
Take me up to the very top!
Ah いつでも無茶ぶり攻めの姿勢
Ah, always unreasonable demands, an offensive stance,
攻めの姿勢
An offensive stance!
誰も止められないし
Nobody can stop me,
踊らずにはいられない
And I can't help but dance!
下向いているそこのかみ...
You down there looking down...
不満ばかりこぼしても意味ないじゃんバカ！
Complaining all the time is meaningless, you fool!
リセットは無し一度きり
No resets, it's a one-time deal,
いつでも真剣勝負ギリ
Always right on the edge of a serious match!
もっともっともっともっともっともっと ワガママになろうぜ！君の人生☆
More and more, let's be selfish! It's your life☆
我慢とかしなくていい そばにいる
You don't have to hold back, I'm right here by your side!
今これからもずっと 約束
Now and forevermore, I promise!
心拍数上げて生きようよ
Let's live with our hearts racing!
退屈奪っていこうよ
Let's steal away the boredom!
ウザいのも 沼って
Even annoying things, get obsessed
好きになっちゃうよ☆
and grow to love them☆
完璧キャラ無理ゲー知らんぷり
Perfect character impossible game, playing dumb,
可愛すぎちゃってグランプリ
Too cute grand prix!
Ah 何でも知りたい 味わいしたい
Ah, I want to know everything, I want to taste it!
味わいしたい
I want to taste it!
誰も止められないし
Nobody can stop me,
歌わずにはいられない
And I can't help but sing!
コンプレックス♡プリンセス
Complex Princess
La La La La La La
一瞬記憶が錯乱するが
My memories are in momentary chaos,
恋は恋だ
but love is love.
お楽しみボディ
A fun body!
愛のボランティア 撫でます ドンッ!!
Volunteer of love, I'll pet you, boom!!
どす恋は辛い
Dosukoi love is tough.
圧倒的な母性と 神さまたち♡
Overwhelming motherhood and the gods♡
勝手に進む 年齢
Age advances on its own,
鳴らない鐘を 鳴らしましょう
so let's ring the silent bell.
私だけを見てくれますか？
Will you only look at me?
ねぇ♡
Hey♡
好き好き好き好き 片思い
Love, love, love, love, unrequited love,
めちゃめちゃめちゃめちゃ 描いたフューチャー
a future I drew so, so much.
大事に大事にして ダーリン
Cherish it carefully, darling.
コンプレックス♡プリンセス
Complex Princess,
よろしくお願いします♡♡♡
please treat me well♡♡♡
コンプレックス♡プリンセス♡
Complex Princess♡
La La La La La La
コンプレックス♡プリンセス♡
Complex Princess♡
La La La La La La
SEXY＆CUTE 全部見せたい 今会いたい♡
SEXY & CUTE, I want to show you everything, I want to meet you now♡
(ようこそ！マリンワールドへ!!)
(Welcome to Marine World!!)
運命共同体 一心同体 側にいたい♡
Community of fate, of one mind, I want to stay by your side♡
(さすがに寂しいわ！愛されたい!!)
(Seriously, I'm lonely! I want to be loved!!)
恋愛 不器用 まである
I'm even clumsy at romance,
(照れなしボンバー)
(shy-less bomber)
ぶっちゃけ 嫉妬の申し子 膝から崩れ落ちろ
frankly, a child of jealousy, collapsing to your knees.
ずっと17歳 もっと愛しなさい！
Always 17, love me more!
夢が大きくて ごめんなさい！
Sorry for having such big dreams!
ホラ♡
Look♡
好き好き好き好き 気付いて
Love, love, love, love, notice me,
手と手 絆を 思い出して
hand in hand, remember our bond.
熱々熱々 力女子力
Passionate, passionate, powerful girlish strength,
自己肯定低い お姫様♡
a low self-esteem princess♡
お迎えに来て 王子様♡
Come pick me up, Prince Charming♡
Ah~ 時には へらる時もあるけど
Ah~ Sometimes I get down in the dumps, but
シナジー全開 海より深い恋心 認知して！ (聞かれていますでしょうか…!?)
synergy full throttle, recognize my love deeper than the sea! (Can you hear us...!?)
Ahoy!
ヨーソロー!
Set sail!
出航!
Departure!
ねぇ♡
Hey♡
好き好き好き好き 片思い
Love, love, love, love, unrequited love,
(Yeah!)
めちゃめちゃめちゃめちゃ 描いたフューチャー
a future I drew so, so much.
(Yeah!)
大事に大事にして ダーリン
Cherish it carefully, darling.
(Yeah!)
コンプレックス♡プリンセス
Complex Princess,
(Yeah!)
君を幸せにします♡♡♡
I will make you happy♡♡♡
コンプレックスプリンセス
Complex Princess,
恋する乙女
a girl in love.
コンプレックスプリンセス♡
Complex Princess♡
生まれ変わるの
I'm being reborn,
キミのプリンセス♡
your princess♡
というわけで なんと つくよみで大人気の かぐやさんに来てもらいました！
And so, Kaguya-san, who is super popular on Tsukuyomi, has come to join us!
イェーイ！イェーイ！かぐや！かぐやだよ！
Yay! Yay! Kaguya! It's Kaguya!
うーわー！かわいいー！
Wow! So cute!
かわいい！ かわいいです！イェーイ！
So cute! So cute! Yay!
まあ、ところですね。初絡みなので、お互いの呼び方とか決めたいんですけど。
Well, since this is our first time interacting, we wanted to decide how to call each other.
おお、いいっすね。ねえ。
Oh, that sounds good. Right.
かぐやは、はい、かぐやで。
Kaguya is... yeah, Kaguya.
ああ、かぐやね。うん。
Ah, Kaguya. Right.
え、じゃあマリンのことは、マリンでもいいし、船長でもいいんですけど、まあ何でもオッケーで。
Uh, then for Marine, you can call me Marine or Senchou, but really anything is fine.
じゃあ、えー、マリンって呼ぶね。
Then, um, I'll call you Marine.
くらっ！くらった！
Ouch! That got me!
呼ぶね！こわこわ！
I'll call you that! Scary, scary!
くらえ！
Take that!
ひっ！かわいい！うー！
Eek! So cute! Woo!
ああ、最高だ。
Ah, this is the best.
ね、マリン、呼んでくれてありがとう！
Hey, Marine, thanks for inviting me!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
いや、すっごいよ、こんなおっきくて素敵なステージで歌えてさ。
Man, it's amazing to sing on such a big, wonderful stage.
もうテンションも爆上げって感じで、超楽しかった！
My tension was completely through the roof, it was super fun!
よかったです！
I'm glad!
でさ、マリンは活動7周年なんだよね？
And you know, Marine is celebrating her 7th anniversary, right?
そうなんです。
That's right.
おめでと！ありがと！おめでと！ありがと！
Congrats! Thanks! Congrats! Thanks!
いや、7年ですよ、7年。
Man, 7 years, 7 years.
すっげえ。
That's amazing.
いや、かぐやはまだまだ新人だと思うんですけど、ちょっとね、かぐやも長く7年、いやそれを超える勢いで長く活動してください！
Well, I think Kaguya is still a newcomer, but Kaguya, please keep being active for a long 7 years, no, even longer than that!
え、当たり前じゃないですか！一緒やるぞ！
Eh, of course! We'll do it together!
一緒やってくれ！かぐや、やるぞ！
Do it together with me! Kaguya, let's do it!
ああ、マリンと、かぐや、一緒やるぞ！一緒やるぞ！行くぞ！
Ah, Marine and Kaguya, let's do it together! Let's do it together! Let's go!
どういうテンションなの？
What kind of tension is that?
まあ、それは置いておいてですね。
Well, leaving that aside...
まあ、今日ね、選曲の話もさせていただきたいと思いますと思います。
Well, today, we'd also like to talk about our song choices.
かぐやのオリジナル曲「私は私のことが好き」とマリンのオリジナル曲「コンプレックスプリンセス」をデュエットしました！しました！
We duetted Kaguya's original song "I Like Myself" and Marine's original song "Complex Princess"! We did!
ではね、このカグラの感情豊かなね、この歌声が大好きで
Well, I just love how emotional and rich Kagura's singing voice is,
もう歌がね、歌唱力が高いだけじゃなく、表現まですごいし
not only is her vocal ability high, but her expression is also amazing,
ね、本当に元気の出る曲で、楽しかったです！
and it's really an energizing song, I had so much fun!
えー、嬉しい！歌唱力も超上がった！
Yay, I'm so happy! My singing skills went way up too!
え、お互いのオリジナル曲を一緒に披露したわけなんですけど、マリンのコンプレックスプリンセス裏ってみてどうでしたか？
We performed each other's original songs together... Marine, how was it trying out "Complex Princess"?
ええ、もうめちゃ楽しかった！お！よかった！
Oh, it was so much fun! Oh, I'm glad!
もうさ、ダンスも可愛いしさ、あとコーラスもめちゃくちゃ楽しい！楽しいよ！
The dance is so cute, and the chorus is also super fun! So fun!
もうみんなと一体になれる感じがさ、もう本当にプリンセスにふさわしい曲だったね！
The feeling of becoming one with everyone... it really was a song fit for a princess!
あ、そうそう、プリンセスだからね、ダブルプリンセス、ダブルプリンセスだよ、私たち。
Ah, that's right, because we're princesses, double princesses, we're double princesses.
そうなんですよう、もう本当に可愛い！もう一生推します！
That's right! It's so cute! I'll oshi you forever!
えい、キュン！あ、可愛すぎる！可愛すぎる。
Take that, kyun! Ah, too cute! Too cute.
最後に、カグラから何か、マリンのチャンネルの視聴者に向けてのメッセージや告知などありますでしょうか？
Lastly, Kagura, is there any message or announcement for Marine's channel viewers?
はい、ございます！みんな、マリンとカグラのコラボステージを見てくれて本当にありがとう！
Yes, there is! Everyone, thank you so much for watching Marine and Kagura's collab stage!
カグラすっごく楽しかったよ！次はツクヤミにも遊びに来てね！来てね！
Kagura had so much fun! Come hang out at Tsukuyomi next time, okay? Come!
そして、カグラも出てる映画「超カグラ姫」が
Also, the movie featuring Kagura, "Cho Kagura-hime,"
9月18日金曜日から、4DXなどの特別フォーマットにパワーアップして上映されることが決定したよ！
has been decided to be screened starting Friday, September 18th, powered up in special formats like 4DX!
おおー！すごーい！新ショウ、うおーすごーい、可愛いよ！
Wooah! Amazing! New show, wooah amazing, so cute!
そうなの、新ショウで撮影したムビチケも売ってるから、みんな絶対買ってね！
That's right, movie tickets shot at Shin-sho are also on sale, so everyone make sure to buy them!
えい！買わなきゃ！買わなきゃ、やったねイエーイ！
Yay! Gotta buy them! Gotta buy them, yay!
そして、12月にツクヤミ感謝祭ってイベントでライブやるんだ！
And, in December, we're holding a live event called the "Tsukuyomi Kanshasai"!
ライブきたー！イエーイきたきたワクワクする！スルスル！みんな絶対に楽しいから来てね！よろしくー！
Live is here! Yay, it's here, I'm so excited! Smoothly! Everyone, it's definitely gonna be fun, so come! Best regards!
いやーもう本当にね、今日のステージ見てね、もうみんなカグラのパフォーマンスにメロメロになったと思うんで、もっと見たいっていう方はぜひもう要チェックとなっております！
Man, I really think everyone who watched today's stage became head over heels for Kagura's performance, so if you want to see more, definitely check it out!
いやーもうマリンもね、もうカグラの魅力に、は、メロメロですよ、本当に。
Man, even Marine is completely head over heels for Kagura's charm, truly.
メロメロでっちょ！あ、メロメロでっちょ！メロメロメロビーム！
Head over heels! Ah, head over heels! Head over heels beam!
でもおね、ちがうメロメロ、あめろめろ、でもマリンのメロメロは、何ね？カグラを娘にしたっていう、そういうメロメロだから。
But you know, a different kind of head over heels... but Marine's head over heels is, what? Wanting to make Kagura her daughter, that kind of head over heels.
えー！なにー？娘に！娘にしたいけどー。えー、娘にしたからー、したいけど、おかしくろ娘。エローピーがうらやましーの。
Eh?! What?! Daughter! I want to make her my daughter, though. Eh, because I made her my daughter, though I want to, but Eropy is envious.
そうだよ、エローピーに怒られちゃうよ。そうだよ、そうだよね、はい、エローピーのものですから、我慢します。
That's right, you'll get yelled at by Eropy. That's right, that's right, yes, because she belongs to Eropy, I'll endure it.
いやあ本当に今度はぜひマリンもツクヤミに呼んでください！
Man really, please invite Marine to Tsukuyomi next time too!
えーもう絶対来てよ！面白いよ絶対！来たい！
Eh, you gotta come! It's super fun for sure! I wanna come!
で、マリンまた一緒にライブしようね！絶対したいです、本当に出たい。本当に今日は来てくれてありがとうございました！
And Marine, let's do a live together again! I definitely want to, I really want to. Thank you so much for coming today!
こちらこそありがとうございました！じゃあまたね、バイバーイ！
Thank you too! See you again, bye-bye!
まるでバーバレラ メロメロよ かなりモーレツにピチピチよん
Head over heels, quite passionately youthful
でもサンデーマンデー… ソリチュード
But Sunday, Monday... Solitude
I love ぜんぶ Mine
I love it all, Mine
ああもう無理 終わり 一体全然かわいらしくないしさ めんどくさいよね？
Ah, I give up, it's not cute at all, so troublesome!
はあ 消えたい
Ha, I want to disappear!
そこがいい！嘘ばっか いい女！
That's what's good! Such lies, good woman!
本当にお宝以上！？ 最後のヒロイン？
Really more than a treasure? The final heroine?
弱気バイバイ スタコラサッサ
Timidity, bye-bye, scamper away
にゃんか元気になってきた！
Somehow I'm getting energized!
サンデーマンデー ソリチュード I love ぜんぶ...
Sunday, Monday, Solitude, I love it all...
私がまたたくたび鳴り響く！
Every time I blink, it resounds!
キャビキャビ
Kyabi kyabi
もっとアイドルでいさせてよ
Let me be an idol even more
きゃぴ (踊 Shake it! Shake it!)
Kyapi (Dance Shake it! Shake it!)
ぎゃぎゃぎゃ…ぎゃぴ
Gyagyagya... gyapi
(1 & 2 & 3 & 4) のシャキシャキね
(1 & 2 & 3 & 4) Crisp and snappy
きゅ、きゅきゅきゅ…きゅるん
Kyu, kyukyukyu... kyurun
まるでバーバレラ メロメロよ
Head over heels like Barbarella
かなりモーレツにピチピチよん
Quite passionately youthful
でもサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ソリチュード
But Sunday, Monday, Sunday, Monday, Sunday, Monday, Solitude
I love ぜんぶ I love ぜんぶ I love ぜんぶ Mine
I love it all, I love it all, I love it all, Mine
ああもう無理 終わり 一体全然かわいらしくないしさ めんどくさいよね？ はあ 消えたい
Ah, I give up, it's not cute at all... So troublesome! Ha, I want to disappear!
そこがいい？ そこがいい！ 嘘ばっか いい女！
Is that good? That's what's good! Such lies, good woman!
いいよなあ？本当に？お宝以上！？ 最後のヒロイン？
Is that good? Really? More than a treasure?! The final heroine?
弱気バイバイ スタコラサッサ
Timidity, bye-bye, scamper away
そそそそうかもね そうだよね！にゃんか元気になってきた！
Ye-ye-yes, maybe so, that's right! Somehow I'm getting energized!
サンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ごめんねキッス
Sunday, Monday, Sunday, Monday, Sunday, Monday, Sorry kiss
サンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ごめんねキッズ
Sunday Monday Sunday Monday Sunday Monday, sorry kids
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ
I love it all, I love it all, I love it all
私が瞬くたび 鳴り響く効果音
Every time I blink, sound effects echo loudly
洗脳してあげる 洗脳してあげる
I'll brainwash you, I'll brainwash you
I'll beat you up! Gonna beat you up!
萌えよSeventeen
Be moe, Seventeen!
接近して感電中 ズッキュンしてバタンキュー
Closing in, getting electrocuted, shot through the heart and knocked out cold
I'll beat you up! Gonna beat you up!
萌えよSeventeen
Be moe, Seventeen!
セクシー×4 破壊的バンビーナ
Sexy x4, destructive bambina
洗脳してあげる ×××してあげない
I'll brainwash you, but I won't do xxx for you
カワイイ？ 顔がいい？ 気持ちがイイ！
Cute? Good-looking? It feels so good!
洗脳シテアゲル アゲル アゲル もっとアイドルでいさせてよ
I'll brainwash you, give it to you, let me be an idol even more!
いくつになっても
No matter how old I get
ギャギャギャギャギャギャギャギャ……きゅぴ
Gya gya gya... kyapi
Mixer! Mixer!
きゅきゅきゅきゅきゅきゅきゅ……きゅるりん
Kyu kyu kyu... kyururin
サンデーマンデーサンデーマンデーサンデーマンデー ソリチュード
Sunday Monday Sunday Monday Sunday Monday, solitude
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ 発作中
I love it all, I love it all, I love it all, having a fit
なんてたってなんてたってなんてたってヘヴィキュート
After all, after all, after all, heavy cute
I Love ぜんぶ I Love ぜんぶ I Love 悪魔の魔の罠
I love it all, I love it all, I love the devil's wicked trap
来世も来々世も 浮気しちゃダメよ
In the next life and the life after that, don't you dare cheat on me!
洗脳してあげる 洗脳してあげる
I'll brainwash you, I'll brainwash you
I'll beat you up! Gonna beat you up!
Forever seventeen
監視して催眠中 ズッキュンしてLovin' You
Watching and hypnotizing, shot through the heart and Lovin' You
I'll beat you up! Gonna beat you up!
萌えよSeventeen
Be moe, Seventeen!
セクシー×4 ごめんねマイダーリン
Sexy x4, sorry my darling
洗脳してあげる もういっそ孕んであげる
I'll brainwash you, I'll even bear your child instead
カワイイ？ 顔がいい？ 気持ちがイイ！
Cute? Good-looking? It feels so good!
洗脳シテアゲル アゲルッタラ ア・ゲル！ もっと I wanna beat you up!
I'll brainwash you, if I say I'll give it to you, I will! I wanna beat you up!
きっと恋するだっちゃ
Surely we'll fall in love, datcha!
ずっとアイドルでいさせてね 神様お願いきゅぴ
Let me stay an idol forever, please God, kyapi!
(ヤババババ 脳内 Shake it! Shake it!)
(Yabababa, shaking up my brain!)
きゅぴぴきゅぴ
Kyapipi kyapi
君たち、マリンの7周年ライブを見てくれてありがとうございました！
Everyone, thank you so much for watching Marine's 7th-anniversary live!
今お披露目した新曲の「きゅぴ」は、配信終了後アニメMVが公開されます。
My new song "Kyapi," which I just debuted, will have its anime MV released after the stream.
マリンの考えるいじめとマリンの関係性とイチャイチャが詰まったMVなので、いっぱい見て、いっぱい一緒にキュンキュンして欲しいです！
The MV is packed with my take on our relationship, so I hope you'll watch and get all fluttery!
見てるうちに曲が頭から離れなくなります。洗脳させてください。
While watching it, the song will get stuck in your head. Please let me brainwash you.
続いて、7周年記念グッズのお知らせです！
Next is an announcement about the 7th-anniversary merchandise!
まずは、B2タペストリー。こちらは今回の新衣装の水着姿をあかさあい先生に描き下ろしていただきました。超美しい！肉感がすごい！絶対飾ってくださいね。
First is the B2 tapestry. Akasa Ai-sensei drew this brand-new swimsuit illustration. It's super gorgeous!
続いて、船長描き下ろしのランダムラバーキーホルダー。デフォルメの絵柄を模索して、これだ！と思えるデフォルメにたどり着いたので、こんな感じで描いてみました。新衣装とまだラバーキーホルダー描いてないなっていう衣装でまとめてみました。かなり可愛いバランスになったかなって自信作なので、ぜひゲットしてくださいね。
Next is the random rubber keychain I drew myself. I found a chibi style that felt just right, so please get them!
続いては、こちら！ぬいぐるみキーホルダーくぢげ風水着衣装ver.。今回の新衣装のデザインでちっちゃくて可愛いぬいぐるみです。お写真を撮った時に楽しげに見えるように、めちゃテンション高い顔に船長が描き下ろしました。楽しい時のお供にしてね。
Next is the plush keychain in a jellyfish swimsuit ver. I drew a super high-energy face for fun photos!
続いてこちら、2way推し事バッグ。船長の新しい衣装の太ももにつけているポーチのデザインとお揃いです。普段使いしやすく、推し活の時には推し活仕様にできるというところを意識しました。シックなデザインなので、これなら日常使いできますよね。
Next is the 2-way oshigoto bag. It matches my new pouch design, perfect for both everyday use and fan activities.
そして、マリンとドキドキ海水浴っていうちょっとラブラブなASMRボイスもあります。ちょっとグイグイかしてもらうんで、覚悟の準備をしておいてください。
There's also a lovey-dovey ASMR voice called "Heart-pounding Beach Trip with Marine." Prepare yourselves!
そしてそして、フルセット購入特典はチケット風カード！昨日ね、夏の野外フェスに出演したところなので、ちょっと意識してサマーフェスチケット風です。通常限定バージョンは直筆メッセージ入り、通常バージョンは複製直筆メッセージ入りです。記念にぜひぜひゲットしてください！
The full set bonus is a summer fest ticket-style card! Please be sure to get it as a keepsake.
そしてこの後はメンバーシップ限定で水着3D撮影会を行います！いろんな差分をお見せするので、いっぱい堪能してくださいね。マリンのメンゲンはゲロ甘らしいので、これを機に他のメンゲンアーカイブと合わせてメンバーシップいかがでしょうか？
After this, we'll hold a membership-only swimsuit 3D photo session! How about joining the membership?
また後日振り返り配信で今日のいろんな裏話を聞いてください。それではいきますよ、しゅっこうー！
Listen to behind-the-scenes stories in a recap stream later. Here we go, set sail!
宝鐘マリン 3D LIVE 4th Anniversary
Houshou Marine 3D LIVE 4th Anniversary
マリン新水着3Dお披露目！
Marine's new swimsuit 3D reveal!